agendize.com 2011-12-14

# Privacy Policy | Agendize

### Scope

At Agendize ("Agendize"), protecting your privacy is very important to us. We treat your personal information with the utmost respect and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy explains how personal information about you may be collected, used, and or disclosed as a consequence of your activities on a website using Agendize technology. We urge you to read it carefully and to print a copy for your records.

By submitting any information through the use of a website which uses Agendize technology (an "Agendize website & services") or by otherwise accessing our site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and consent to the policies and practices described for the collection, use and or disclosure of personal information and you expressly consent to the collection, storage, use and or disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

### Data Collection

The type of personal information that is protected varies from one jurisdiction to another but generally includes any information concerning an identifiable individual, such as name, address, telephone number, age, sex, marital status and nationality, etc. Personal information may not, however, include certain types of business or employment related information. It generally does not, for example, include the name, title, business address or telephone number of an employee of an organization. Such information is not usually considered personal information.

You may visit an Agendize website at any time without submitting personal information. When you visit such website, or when you visit third-party websites providing content that uses Agendize services, data is saved on our servers in an anonymous format, such as, for example, connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the Agendize website & services, and ad data. Also saved is the identification of the website that you arrive from, the website that you proceed to from our site, and your IP address. In collecting this information, no personal data is associated with you. We may share such data in an anonymous format with third parties, including, but not limited to, vendors that support the operation of our website and services, and entities involved in the delivery of advertisements.

We do, however, require some information, which may include personal information, so that you can actively use the features of the Agendize website & services. Once you provide Agendize or the owner of the Agendize website (hereinafter "us" or "we") with your required personal information, you are no longer anonymous. In providing us with your personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of such information on our servers, in order to serve you.

Once you are registered, we may some or all of the following personal information:

  * email address and physical contact information, including but not limited to your name, address, date of birth and telephone number;
  * all transactional information based on your activities on the Agendize website;
  * any correspondence sent to us; and
  * other supplemental information from third parties who are permitted to communicate such information to us.

The database containing your personal information will be assigned to the owner of the Agendize website & services.

Apart from the preceding, we do not collect, use or disclose your personal information without your consent except where required or allowed by law. We do not knowingly solicit information from children and we do not knowingly market our services to minors. Your personal information is located on a server situated in Montréal, Québec, Canada. We will take reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information is as accurate, complete and up-to-date as is appropriate for its purpose.

### Use of Data

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. You agree that we may use your personal information to:

  * provide the services and customer support you request;
  * customize, measure and improve our services, content and advertising;
  * resolve disputes, collect fees and troubleshoot problems;
  * prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities; 
  * inform you about our services, targeted marketing, service updates and promotional offers; and
  * compare information for accuracy and verify it with authorized third parties.

We agree to protect the confidentiality of your personal information as much as reasonably possible while doing so.

We routinely update personal information to fulfill the purposes for which the information was collected, as outlined in this Privacy Policy. You expressly consent to our routinely updating your personal information and, where appropriate, soliciting such updates from you.

### Disclosure

We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims content violates the rights of others, or protect third party rights, property or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations in the province of Quebec and Canada.

We may also share your personal information with third parties assisting our business operations under contract or seeking our co-operation, including but not limited to: vendors that support the operation of our website and services such as billing and payment systems, fraud investigators and debt collection agencies and personnel; law enforcement or other governmental officials if required by law; and, other business entities, should we plan to merge with or be acquired by those business entities, provided such business entities have signed a non-disclosure agreement.

Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, government officials or other third parties without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except where we believe, in good faith, that the disclosure of such information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity.

### Public Computer

When visiting an Agendize website & services from a public or shared computer, certain information about you may be visible to others who use such computer after you.

### Access

Your information, which may include your personal information, can only be modified by contacting the AgendiZe customer service department. Such department may require additional information from you in order to verify your identity following an access request. Such personal information will only be used for the purpose of identity verification and will itself be subject to protection under the terms of this Privacy Policy. You are required to promptly update your personal information if changes occur or if any information is inaccurate.

### Revoking Consent

You may withdraw your consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information at any time by contacting the customer service department of the relevant Agendize website & services. Upon such request, we will remove your personal information from our systems as soon as reasonably possible, in accordance with applicable law. We do retain certain personal information from closed files, separately from the information relative to active files, in order to comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms of Service, and take other actions otherwise required and or permitted by law.

### Cookies

We use so-called "cookies" which are files that are stored on your computer that can be retrieved to assist in customizing your experience with the online service. They are used to help us measure the number of visits, average time spent, page views, and other statistics relating to your use of this site. This cookie, by itself, does not tell us your email address or who you are. You are free to prevent cookies from being saved on your hard drive by adjusting the corresponding settings in your browser. However, turning off these settings may result in limited functionality.

### Security Measures

Please remember to log out of your account and to close your internet browser window when you leave an Agendize website & services; this is especially important if you use a computer in public locations (You may also wish to delete your browsing history after each visit to an Agendize website & services; again, this is critical if you use a computer in public locations. At present, this is the safest way to ensure that no one has access to your personal information. We assume no liability for the abuse of any information remaining on a computer that is used by a third party.

We treat data as an asset that must be protected. Although we use all reasonable means to ensure that the information you provide to us is not used by third parties for purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy, we are not responsible for any improper use of your personal information that is beyond our reasonable control.

### Unsolicited Information

In addition to your username, any comments or submissions ("Unsolicited Information") that you post on our website or services will be publicly available. All such Unsolicited Information will be deemed to be non-confidential and AgendiZe will be free to reproduce, use, disclose and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution. You should be aware that, if you voluntarily disclose Unsolicited Information online, that Unsolicited Information can be collected and used by others. For example, if you post your email address in comments sections or online forums, you may receive unsolicited messages from others. AgendiZe has no control over the use of personally identifiable information that you voluntarily post in public forums or otherwise disclose while interacting with other users. Any such personally identifiable information you choose to disclose should reflect how much you want other users to know about you. We encourage our clients and visitors to think carefully about what information they disclose in their comments or submissions.

### Spam

Should we obtain your e-mail address, mobile phone number, fax number, instant messaging and or social media accounts, we will not rent or sell any such information to third parties, and we will endeavour to prevent your e-mail address from being recorded by "web crawlers" or "web spiders" to the best of our ability. If you believe that your e-mail address has been recorded in this way, please let us know immediately.

### Our clients

The various owners of Agendize website & services have agreed to abide by this Privacy Policy, in the same manner as Agendize. While we can monitor our sites and our clients' sites, we have no control over third party websites; however, we make efforts to require our clients to ensure that any third party website post adequate privacy policies and otherwise protect the privacy rights of their visitors. Check the privacy policies of such third party websites using our services for information regarding their applicable privacy practices.

### General

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms herein. All amended terms take effect immediately once they are posted on the Agendize website.
